[
    {
        "front": "きせつ",
        "back": "季節 \nseason",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しき",
        "back": "四季 \nfour seasons",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "きせつ",
        "back": "季節 \nseason",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "せつぶん",
        "back": "節分 \nfestival celebrated at the time of winter",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "はる",
        "back": "春 \nspring season",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "せいしゅん",
        "back": "青春 \nyouth",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつ",
        "back": "夏 \nsummer",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつやすみ",
        "back": "夏休み \nsummer holidays",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつまつり",
        "back": "夏祭り \nsummer festival",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "なつふく",
        "back": "夏服 \nsummer clothes",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あき",
        "back": "秋 \nautumn",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あきたけん",
        "back": "秋田県 \nAkita prefecture",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふゆ",
        "back": "冬休み \nwinter",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふゆやすみ",
        "back": "冬休み \nwinter holidays",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゅんかしゅうとう",
        "back": "春夏秋冬 \nall seasons",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あつい",
        "back": "暑い \nhot weather",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひしょち",
        "back": "避暑地 \nsummer resort",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "ざんしょ",
        "back": "残暑 \nlate summer heat",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "さむい",
        "back": "寒い \ncold weather",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんたい",
        "back": "寒帯 \ncold zone",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "かんぱ",
        "back": "寒波 \ncold wave",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "あたたかい",
        "back": "暖かい \nwarm",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "おんだん",
        "back": "温暖 \nwarm weather",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "だんぼう",
        "back": "暖房 \nheater",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "すずしい",
        "back": "涼しい \ncool weather",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    },
    {
        "front": "りょうふう",
        "back": "涼風 \ncool breeze",
        "chapter": "N4 K8"
    }
]